♪The world keeps changing♪
♪A thousand years pass
in the blink of an eye♪
♪Shoulder to shoulder♪
♪We stand above the world♪
♪Our identities switch♪
♪The world turns upside down♪
♪Watch me♪
♪Stir up a storm♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our blood is boiling♪
♪The genius emperor plots
with brilliant strategy♪
♪The slacker general
is unmatched in battle♪
♪The business world is in turmoil♪
♪The court is rife with intrigue♪
♪We will conquer the world♪
♪There's no escape for the traitors♪
=No Way! My Bro Is the Emperor=
=Episode 21=
Your Majesty.
How was it?
Have you found Gu Bei?
Official Gu
is at the Princess Royal's residence.
Her Highness asked me
to deliver this letter to you.
Aunt
wants to marry Gu Bei?
I didn't know
you were this skilled.
A good blacksmith needs solid skills.
A boss who can't do the job
isn't a good boss.
(What is Gu Bei up to now?)
Your Majesty, you're here.
Please have a seat.
I've come today
to confirm what was written
in your letter.
Your Majesty, you know
I've been alone for years
and have never found a suitable husband.
But ever since I met Gu Bei,
I knew
he was the one for me.
Aunt,
I'm afraid
this matter still needs discussion.
Gu Bei.
Put that down.
Come back to the palace with me.
I have something
to discuss with you.
I wish to resign.
Are you defying my decree?
I wouldn't dare.
It's just that...
The Princess Royal is the big boss.
I'd rather
stay by her side.
(Big boss?)
(Bei's telling me)
(the Princess Royal is the mastermind.)
Your Majesty,
why force him?
Ever since I met Her Highness,
I've realized
what truly matters in life.
Titles and future mean nothing.
It's like an old man from my village.
Yu
Ze
cheng.
(Bei's going undercover.)
Who's this Yu Zecheng?
Just an old man from my village.
He
spent his whole life chasing fame,
but in the end,
he
died alone.
I've never asked you for anything.
I only hope
you'll grant us your blessing.
Aunt, I'm deeply grateful
for your support when I chose my empress.
As for your marriage to Gu Bei,
I'll leave it to the two of you.
Your Majesty,
it's time to
give me today's antidote.
"Big boss".
What is that?
It's a dialect from my village.
It means master.
How do you plan
to get rid of Xiao Ce?
Don't worry, Your Majesty.
A party will do.
"Party"?
Is that another village saying?
Yes, Your Majesty.
It means a banquet.
Have you heard?
(Xiaoyao Pavilion)
Gu Bei's marrying the Princess Royal.
I don't believe it.
Do you really think
Gu Bei would abandon us?
Neither do I.
But he's moved
into the Princess Royal's residence,
and refuses to see us.
I don't think
he's refusing to see us.
Perhaps he can't.
You mean
he's being controlled?
Why else
(Xiaoyao Pavilion)
would he send word
telling us to paint the door?
Your Majesty,
what's
Gu Bei really up to?
He has his reasons.
Whatever he's doing,
it's for our sake.
If so, let's trust him.
Let's get to work.
You all do it.
You!
What are you doing?
You should ask Gu Bei.
He sent word
saying that
there'll be a banquet in a few days.
He insisted
we paint the door red.
A red door?
A banquet?
The banquet by the Western Yi
is a setup.
Your Majesty,
the Western Yi envoys
have been in the capital for days
and wish for an audience.
Let's hold a banquet
in the imperial garden.
The Western Yi envoys
submitted a memorial,
saying palace etiquette
is too strict.
They're afraid
they might offend Your Majesty.
They request permission
to host a private banquet
outside the palace.
Granted.
But where
should it be held?
Why not
at Gu Bei's
Xiaoyao Pavilion?
You really dote on him.
We'll do as you wish, Aunt.
We'll host the envoys
at Xiaoyao Pavilion.
(The Best Pavilion in the World)
What
is this?
Fried popcorn chicken.
It cuts through grease.
Eat as much as you want.
Emperor of Jing,
I've never seen
a restaurant like this.
Thank you for your hospitality.
Allow me to offer you a toast.
This is
the Western Yi's
finest grape wine.
Please.
This won't do.
How can His Majesty drink
without appetizers?
Hulv.
Bring His Majesty the cefixime.
That's more like it.
Cefixime and wine
make quite the combination.
(Bei's warning me)
(the wine is poisoned.)
To everyone from far and wide,
beautiful ladies
and gentlemen,
let us drink
this toast together.
Drink!
- Drink!
- Cheers!
If the poison fails
during the banquet,
the Western Yi envoys
will take the chance
to finish Xiao Ce off.
Your Majesty,
I've heard the Western Yi people
are good at dancing.
Why not have them perform
to liven up the banquet?
Very well.
We'll trouble you, envoy.
Your Majesty,
our dance
requires swords.
May I
use them?
Certainly.
Come.
Bring him a sword.
(The Best Pavilion in the World)
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our spirit soars to the skies♪
♪The brainy emperor plots the strategy♪
♪The slacker general leads the charge♪
♪Swords clash and warhorses thunder♪
♪Let the history judge our deeds♪
♪Our brotherhood is priceless♪
♪Peace across the land, carefree at last♪
♪Funny moments never stop♪
♪Silly blunders never cease♪
♪Yet through every up and down♪
♪We create miracles♪
♪From naive youths♪
♪To legendary heroes♪
♪This journey♪
♪Is one we'll be proud of♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Let's create♪
♪A legend of our own♪